We found that to
be a false positive
It's almost like a
And it's very scary
when we cross that
data Because when we
found our biggest most
significant markups our biggest
outcomes that drive fund
returns a lot of
them were just ideas
They start off they
had very little traction
But what else did
they have is that
they had a business
model that you can
call them copycats but
not essentially copycats but
they already have a
of references that sized
up the that made
it a more familiar
of a business model
So if you can
get in at those
types of companies those
patterns and that kind
of how we invest
in today we're not
totally attracted by just
traction alone We need
to make sure that
this traction is you
to somewhere big I'll
kind of make it
crispy the way of
saying it is like
this It's easy to
find a good idea
but it's a harder
to a big idea
Not all good ideas
are big ideas right
So that's kind of
like one big lesson
from our decade of
investing here